

Esmir Neretljak

Software Engineer

Hardworking and motivated with 2.5 years in IT environment. Extremely ambiguous and hungry to learn more and improve my programming skills and others as well.

Willing to learn new skills and knowledges. Progressive and highly organized.

Dedicated to personal development. Looking for a chance where I will be able to devote to full time programming.

Email: esmirneretljak@gmail.com **Address:** Prvomajska 33, Sarajevo

Phone: +387 62/927-323

Github: https://github.com/Esmir-dev **Nationality:** Bosnia & Hercegovina

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/esmir-neretljak/

Experience

Jul 2020 - Apr 2022

Data Specialist

Checklens (IT Company) Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

- · Proactively participated in meetings and helped create new practices.
- · Handled customer complaints with empathy and composure.
- Testing AI models
- Training AI models
- Prototyping
- · Architecture and design

Nov 2019 - Jun 2020

Data Analist

PixIbrain (IT Company) Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

- Training AI models
- · Testing AI models
- · Collection data for products
- Worked with AI software for food market
- · Collection and manipulation with data

May 2019 - Oct 2019

Part Time / External Contractor

Work & Travel Experience Ocean City (United States of America)

• Worked in various positions in the field of tourism; hotels, souvenir shops, restaurants

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

Part Time / External Contractor **DHL Germany** Hamburg (Germany)

Sorted and distributed mail, packages and letters

Jul 2017 - Sep 2017

Part Time / External Contractor

SHW AG & Georg Fischer Tuttlingen & Singen (Germany)

- Production of brake discs for cars (BMW, Audi, Porsche, Passat)
- · Production of auto parts, control and work on assembly line

Jul 2015 - Sep 2015

Part Time / External Contractor

BMW Munchen (Germany)

· Assistance to permanent employees, in production and cleaning of facilities

Education

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022

Paragon (IT Program for full stack developer)

Mistral Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Program for full stack developers, which lasted 11 months, in one of the best Sarajevo IT companies, Mistral

2022 - 2022

Coding Challenge

Mistral Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Won the coding challenge, with an application for the digitization of the health system of Canton Sarajevo, together with three other members of my team.

2019 - 2022

MA / Regional and Spatial planning

Faculty of Science/ University of Sarajevo Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

· Sustainable development of the development of a certain area, and environmental protection

2014 - 2018

BA / Regional and Spatial planning

Faculty of Science / University of Sarajevo Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

• Sustainable development of the development of certain area, and environmental protection

2008 - 2012

High School

Gazi Husrev-begova medresa Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Languages

English Language

Advanced. Poliglota /

Sarajevo

German Language

Elementary. Poliglota /

Sarajevo

Arabic Language / High

School

Elementary

Skills

Problem-Solving

Architecture and design

Machine Learning

ΑI

Teamwork

Customer service

Planning

Adaptability

Html

Css

Java Script

React

Node Js

Mongo Db

Leadership

html5

html6

bootstrap

Jira react-bootstrap

material-ui

react-icons

awesome-font

express

Interpersonal Skills

Management

Geographic

Microsoft Office

Information Systems

(GIS)